So after a couple of very long videos,
let's now take a breath and take a minute
to discuss our next step in implementing this project.
So at this point, we have implemented all the features
from one to seven, and now all that is left to do
is steps eight, nine, and 10,
which are all about the user being able
to upload their own recipes.
So, whenever the user clicks the ad recipe button,
that's in the menu bar, all we want to do
is to display a recipe editor.
So that's like a model window which will pop up
and which contains a form.
Then on that form, we will have to bind an event handler
so that when the user submits that form.
So here in this diagram that means
when the user creates a new recipe
then of course we want to asynchronously
upload that recipe to the API.
And we will also want to render that recipe
and also edit to the user's bookmarks.
And so that is a feature number nine here
in our feature lists.
So basically that all our own recipes
are automatically bookmarked.
Finally, all this is going to be set up in a way
that only the user that uploaded the recipe
will be able to see that recipe.
So for example, if I upload my own pizza recipe
then if you search for pizza afterwards
you will not be able to see that recipe.
So these recipes are really gonna belong to you.
And as I mentioned before,
we will do that by using an API developer key.
So, these are the last steps that we need to take
in order to finish our application.
And so let's start by doing that in the next lecture,
starting with the simple functionality
of displaying the window, when the user clicks add recipe